Guide to the Ellen McGowan Biddle Shipman papers, 1914-1946.
Shipman, Ellen McGowan Biddle papers, 1914-1946.
- Series IV. Project Files (Plans)
  - Mrs. James Parmelee (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting plan for garden - Sheet B (Black and White), 1915 (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting plan for flower garden, 1915 (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Shrub planting plan for around porch, undated (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting plan of shrubbery screen, undated (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting plan, 1915 (Map-case Folder 104a)
  - Unknown (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Construction plan of gate to laundry yard (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Detail of gate (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting and construction plan for a city walled garden (Horticulture, Inc.), undated (Map-case Folder 104a)
  - The Misses Pryne (Mary Pruyn) (Map-case Folder 105)
    Location: East Hampton, New York
    - Construction plan of garden (x2), 1919 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Details of pool, 1919 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Shrub and bulb planting plan, 1920 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Perennial planting plan, 1920 (Map-case Folder 105)
  - Julian Peabody (Map-case Folder 105-106)
    - Planting plan of flower border, 1924 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan of rose garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 105)
      Location: Huntington, Long Island, New York
    - Sketches, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Construction drawing for north terrace (VOID), 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Planting plan for north terrace, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Suggestion for well-head, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Design plan for flower garden - Sketch A, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Sketch of area fronting residence, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Construction drawing for north terrace, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Planting plan for north boundary screen, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Planting plan for highway screen, 1945 (Map-case Folder 106)
  - A.J.D. Paul (Map-case Folder 105)
    Location: Radnor, Pennsylvania
    - Plan showing changed location of shrubs in truck garden, 1916 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan for rose garden, 1916 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan of flower garden (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Design sketch for rose garden (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Sketch of garden changes (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Construction plan of pool in garden (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan of perennial garden (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Revised construction details of steps, walls, terraces (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan of terrace (Map-case Folder 105)
  - Miss. L. Parsons (Map-case Folder 105)
    Location: Kennebunk, Maine
    - Preliminary plan for flower garden, 1914 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan for flower garden, 1914 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan for area surrounding turnaround, 1914 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Construction plan for flower garden, 1914 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - Planting plan of border, 1914 (Map-case Folder 105)
    - General planting plan (Map-case Folder 105)
  - Geoffry Platt (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Sketch of existing topography (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Design plan, 1946 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Grading plan (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Grading plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 106)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Earl N. Phillips (Map-case Folder 106)
    Location: High Point, North Carolina
    - Construction details for swimming pool (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Layout sketch of bath houses and pool (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Preliminary sketch of swimming pool area (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Topographical map of portion of estate (2 Black and White and Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Rose border in play ground (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Planting plan along boundary (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Sketch plan for terrace (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Planting plan for terrace pool, wall, paving and steps (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Construction plan for playground walls and steps (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Driveway planting plan (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Sketch plan and layout plan (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Construction plan for stone wall, seat and steps (Map-case Folder 106)
  - Mr. and Mrs. David Prince (Map-case Folder 106)
    Location: Schenectady, New York
    - Sketch of the property (Black and White), 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Design for west terrace garden (2 Black and Whites), 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Planting plan for dining terrace, 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Screen planting plan (Blueprint), 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Tree, shrub, and vine planting plan (Blueprint), 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Perennial planting plan for living terrace (Blueprint), 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Construction drawing for flagstone terrace, 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Sketches, 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Construction details for pool, 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Suggestion for further development, 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Screen planting plan for north boundary, 1942 (Map-case Folder 106)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Thomas L. Perkins (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Topographic map (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Design plan (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Survey of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 106)
    - Design plan for further development (Map-case Folder 106)
  - Miss Sarah Potter (Map-case Folder 107)
    Location: Westport, Connecticut
    - Trellis and seat details (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Details of garden seat around pool - Sheet 1 (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Details of garden seat around pool - Sheet 2 (Map-case Folder 107)
  - Herbert Pratt (Map-case Folder 107)
    Location: Mill Neck, Long Island, New York
    - Construction details for wooden door in drying yard (Map-case Folder 107)
  - Mr. and Mrs. William A. Parker (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Planting plan for pool garden (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Planting plan for spring flowers under cherries (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Preliminary sketch plan of garden (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Preliminary sketch plan of grounds (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Construction details for pool (Map-case Folder 107)
    - General plan of estate (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 107)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Henry T. Peters (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Perennial planting plan of garden (2 copies) (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Bulb planting plan of garden (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Proposed changes in garden (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Construction details for steps (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Construction details and plan of terrace (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Construction plan of garden (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Topographical plan of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Construction plan for walls and steps (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Location plan of hedge (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Topographic map (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 107)
    - Shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 107)
  - Mrs. E.J. Plumb (Map-case Folder 108)
    Location: Shelter Island, New York
    - Perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Two sketches of planting plan near existing cedars, identical, undated (Map-case Folder 108)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Redfield Proctor (Map-case Folder 108)
    Location: Proctor, Vermont
    - Perennial planting plan, 1935 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Revised design plan (Black and White), 1935 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan, 1935 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Sketches, 1935 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Construction plan for flower garden, 1935 (Map-case Folder 108)
  - Mrs. George Patton (Map-case Folder 108)
    Location: Riverview, Tennessee
    - Planting plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Planting plan for spring flowers (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Planting plan for perennials (VOID) (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Construction drawing for stone steps (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Preliminary drawing for casino (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 108)
  - Mrs. Rodney Proctor (Map-case Folder 108)
    Location: Stockbridge, Massachusetts
    - Screen planting of trees (Map-case Folder 108)
  - Mr. and Mrs. W.A. Paddock (Map-case Folder 108)
    - General design plan (Blueprint), 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint), 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Sketch, 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Floor plans of house (Blueprint), 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
  - Mrs. George Putnam (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Construction plan for flower garden, 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Revised design planting plan of flower garden, 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Sketches, 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Map (Blueprint), 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Preliminary design plan, 1936 (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Topographic map (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 108)
  - Prentice (Map-case Folder 108)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 108)
  - Mrs. R.S. Richards (Map-case Folder 109 and Box 14)
    Location: Sewickly, Pennsylvania
    - Plot plan, 1947 (Map-case Folder 109)
    - Plan for cemetery lot - I (matted), 1947 (Box 14)
    - Plan for cemetery lot - II (matted), 1947 (Box 14)
  - Mrs. R. Ratliff (Map-case Folder 109)
    Location: Stockton, New Jersey
    - Dimension plan for flower garden, 1941 (Map-case Folder 109)
    - Planting plan for standards and shrubs, 1941 (Map-case Folder 109)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Edward Riley (Map-case Folder 109)
    Location: Lumberville, Pennsylvania
    - Preliminary design plan (Blueprint), 1939 (Map-case Folder 109)
    - Sketches, 1939 (Map-case Folder 109)
    - Topographic map - Sheet I and II (Blueprint), 1939 (Map-case Folder 109)
    - Topographic map of entire property (Blueprint), 1939 (Map-case Folder 109)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Jefferson Robinson (Map-case Folder 110)
    Location: Toledo, Ohio
    - Design plan (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Construction drawing for entrance drive (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Residence screen planting - Section A (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Key to screen planting (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Roadside planting - Section B (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Topographic survey (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Roadside screen planting - Section C (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Screen planting along dividing fence - Section 1 (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Screen planting along dividing fence - Section 2 (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Roadside screen planting - Section D (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Preliminary report of topographic survey (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 110)
    - Preliminary design plan A-E (Blueprints and Black and Whites) (Map-case Folder 110)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J.S. Rockefeller (Map-case Folder 111-112)
    - Planting plan for flower garden, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Planting plan - trees and shrubs along service drive, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - General design plan, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Planting plan for east steps, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Planting plan for entrance, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Construction drawing for arch at garage, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Construction drawing for gate in hedge around swimming pool, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Planting plan for garage screen, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Planting plan for perennials for upper terrace, 1938 (Map-case Folder 111)
    - Measured drawing for dining terrace lattice, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Drawing for wisteria support, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J.V. Reed (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Construction drawing for walls and steps in existing garden (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Finials for bath houses (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Preliminary design plan - A, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Construction plan for stone seat, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Alternative plan for rose garden (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - South terrace railing (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Sketches, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Plan for estimate for house, terraces, walls and steps, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Plans of house (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Details of bluestone steps on south terraces (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Preliminary design plan - B, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Plan for laying out rose beds, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Construction details for steps on south terrace, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Construction drawing for tennis court wall, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Design plan (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Revised design plan, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Planting plan for swimming pool area, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Topographic map (Blueprint), 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Planting plan for house terraces, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Construction plan and details for terraces, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Plan for revision of front entrance, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
    - Planting plan for rose garden, 1938 (Map-case Folder 112)
  - Miss Julia Ryle (Map-case Folder 113)
    Location: Mount Kisko (Katonah), New York
    - Planting plan of garden, 1917 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Planting plan of garden - Sheets A-C, 1916 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Shrub planting plan, 1916 (Map-case Folder 113)
  - Mr. Lansing Reed (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Construction details for iron supports (2 copies), 1929-1930 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Revised construction plan for garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Shrub planting plan, 1926 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Flower planting plan, 1926 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Sketch plan for the garden and estate, undated (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Bulb planting plan, undated (Map-case Folder 113)
    - General construction plan, 1925 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Planting plan for rose garden, undated (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Two sketches for rose trellis, 1927 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Topographic map - plan for water supply and drainage (Blueprint), 1925 (Map-case Folder 113)
    - Construction plan for cold frames, undated (Map-case Folder 113)
    - General landscape design for trees and shrubs, undated (Map-case Folder 113)
  - Mr. W.W. Reese (Map-case Folder 114)
    - Perennial planting plan - Section A and B, 1936 and 1939 (Map-case Folder 114)
    - Bulb planting plan - Section A and B, 1939 (Map-case Folder 114)
    - Bulb planting plan sketch - Section A and B, 1939 (Map-case Folder 114)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (Blueprint photostat), 1939 (Map-case Folder 114)
    - Sketches, 1939 (Map-case Folder 114)
    - Details of flagstone paving, 1939 (Map-case Folder 114)
  - Mr. and Mrs. A.M. Rust (Map-case Folder 115)
    Location: Saginaw, Michigan
    - Planting plan for shrubs on south boundary (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Design plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 115)
  - Mr. and Mrs. William Reed (Map-case Folder 115)
    Location: Sabot, Virginia
    - Revised design plan, 1938 (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Plan for alternate location of tennis court (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Preliminary design plan, 1938 (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Topographic map of property (Blueprint), 1937 (Map-case Folder 115)
    - Grading plan of drives (Blueprint), 1937 (Map-case Folder 115)
  - Mrs. Ellen Shipman (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Rose arches for brook place (Map-case Folder 116)
  - St. Gaudens Memorial (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Flower planting plan (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Construction plan for changes in garden (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Revised planting plan for flower garden (Map-case Folder 116)
  - Mr. and Mrs. F.D. Suydam (Map-case Folder 116)
    Location: White Mills, Pennsylvania
    - Design plan (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Design plan photograph (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Plan for herb garden (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Sketch plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Revised design plan (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Survey for lollypop pool section (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 116)
    - Plan in vicinity of Suydam house (Map-case Folder 116)
  - Philip Spalding (Map-case Folder 117)
    Location: Hylan Street, Milton, Massachusetts
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Planting plan for kitchen garden (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Sketch plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Plan showing location of trees (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Bulb planting plan for borders of house terrace (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Construction details for fruit tree posts (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Bulb planting plan for perennial border vegetable garden (Whiteprint) (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Vegetable planting plan (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Shrub planting plan - bed near greenhouse (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Topographical plan of land (Whiteprint) (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Layout of grounds (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Sketch plan for terrace (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Revised shrub planting plan border below terrace (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Planting plan for tulips - Sheet 1 and 2 (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Construction plan and details for terrace, walls, and steps (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Planting plan for terrace (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Construction plan for brick walk (Map-case Folder 117)
      Location: Marion, Massachusetts
    - Plan showing location of trees, drive, and tennis court (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Boundary planting pf trees and shrubs (Map-case Folder 117)
    - Design plan for flower garden (Whiteprint) (Map-case Folder 117)
  - Mrs. W.B. Sharp (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Design plan showing revisions (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Planting plan for shrubs along drive (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Construction drawing for brick terrace (Map-case Folder 118)
  - F. Stranahan (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Construction drawing for limestone coping of pool in octagonal garden (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Diagram of changes in octagonal garden (Whiteprint) (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Well head sketches (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Stone coping detail (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Revised construction drawing for sandstone coping for pool (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Plan for screen planting along driveway (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Planting to screen neighboring house (Map-case Folder 118)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Duane Stranahan (Map-case Folder 118, 131, 136-137)
    Perrysburg, Ohio
    - Arbor planting plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 118)
    - Wrought iron railing detail drawing (Map-case Folder 131)
    - Architectural details for the old stable, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Construction drawing for rose arch, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Preliminary design plan (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Planting plan for perennials in flower garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs in flower garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Design plan for flower garden (2 Black and White), 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Construction drawing for flower garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Details of terrace and walk paving, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Construction drawing for trellis, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Details of trellis, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Planting plan for northwest side of house, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Plan of vegetable and picking garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Construction drawing for driveway and entrance court, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Site plan (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Design plan (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Revised construction drawing for driveway and entrance court, 1944 (Map-case Folder 136)
    - Construction drawing for gate in entrance court, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Planting plan for shrubs to screen service drive, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Planting plan for entrance court (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - First floor plan (Black and White), 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Sketches, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Revised plan for cut to ravine(Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Construction drawing for wrought iron rail, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Tree location plan, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Plan for cut to ravine (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Planting plan for cut to ravine, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Topographical survey of outlots 193 and 194 (2 Blueprints), 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Plan for staking driveway, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Plan for location of 3 apple trees, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Planting plan for cut to ravine, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Details for grass steps, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Construction plan for flagstone terrace, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Planting plan for boundary screen, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Revised plan for cut to ravine, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
    - Construction drawing for lath fence around laundry yard, 1944 (Map-case Folder 137)
  - Mr. and Mrs. I.T. Starr (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Forecourt planting plan, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Planting plan for garden - Sheet B, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Planting plan for pond, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Detail of flower planting, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - General planting plan, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Revised planting plan for garden - Sheet B, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Planting plan for garden - Sheet A, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Planting plan for shrubs, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
    - Planting plan for railroad screen, 1916 (Map-case Folder 119)
  - Mr. and Mrs. R.A. Stranahan (Map-case Folder 120-124)
    - Plans and elevations for bath house (Blueprint), 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Swimming pool coping, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Construction details for swimming pool, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Revisions to bath house (blueprint), 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Construction plan for flower gardens, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Details of iron pergola (3 Blueprints), 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Casino - east, west and north elevations, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
      See Folder 122 for more casino plans
    - Casino plan, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Perennial planting plan for upper garden, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Planting plan for perennials and roses, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Tree, shrubs, and vines planting plan, 1936 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Bulb planting plan for upper and lower gardens, 1938 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Revised bulb planting plan for lower garden, 1941 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - House and gardens (6 photostats), 1941 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Design of iron grille, 1941 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Design plan for the swimming pool area, 1941 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Design plan - May, 1937 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Design plan - June, 1937 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Revised design plan - July, 1937 (Map-case Folder 120)
    - Plan showing location of large trees, 1937 (Map-case Folder 120)